{
    "id": "cb59decd9239487e969b9ea74741bd3f",
    "title": "Since And For",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been associated with this organization ………………… ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11061efba79b491585d75ae57425f41a"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother has been ailing …………………. July.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b31d38b4b2784fd7b85a6a2f2d14cff8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… when have you been living in this city?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7fd7043662204e47b48e581f33c39f26"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have been learning Latin ………………….. six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73404ea54d494782a6c08a7392aa9fd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister has been learning music …………………. January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1dfeddf15de2429086d87c190f830bd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked as a waiter ………………….. six years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83f758d0d62744259ef6c95019da6d5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been practicing Yoga ………………….. six years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89d425a6452f47e0998c62d422d1ead8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… when have you been learning music?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f11f67728109402eabd2b61926852ab8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been living in this city ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70ca70b84e8746439f596bef31235857"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been ten years ………………… I retired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "391b35b853894a348bd53c929669e11f"
        }
    ]
}